+917358456006

Plot no: 2 flat "e" Dhenupuree apts Old Jothi nagar 1<sup>st</sup> street Madambakkam Chennai -600126 TAMILNADU, INDIA.

### **KARTHICK R**

#### **SENIOR TECHNICAL LEAD**

Senior Technical Lead with more than four years of experience in Automobile Industry at vehicle Service & Delivery process .Involved in Service Supervision, Quality Service Process and Technical Support in BS IV & BS VI Technologies.

## **Working Experience**

M/s Shree Motors Agencies Pvt. Ltd. (VECV Authorized Dealer) May2016-present

- Joined as Engineering Trainee in the company (May 2016 –December 2016)
- With excelled performance promoted as Service Advisor (January 2017- March 2018)
- With continuous training and learning given from the company became Senior Technical Lead (April 2018-present)
- Well trained in Warranty Process, Accident and Insurance claims.

## **CORE COMPETENCY SKILLS**

- Analyzing and approving warranty claims under constrained limits
- Checking and providing quality service process as per quality norms
- Checking and maintaining safety standards in work area as per ISO standards
- Resolving customer complaints to their needs with quick response
- Fault tracing and providing technical assistance in BS VI technologies
- Analyzing vehicle crash and prepare repair estimate
- Posses experience at OEM service in WABCO products

# **Education Qualification**

- B.E. Mechanical Engineering passed out with 6.904cgpa (August2012-April2016)
  Agni College of Technology.
- HSC (12<sup>th</sup>) passed out with 86.6% (March 2012)
  Zion Matriculation Higher Secondary School.
- SSLC (10<sup>th</sup>) passed out with 78.4% (March 2010) Zion Matriculation Higher Secondary School.

#### **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that the above information is true to the best of my knowledge.